LAUREN CHEN

DIGITAL MARKETING SPECIALIST

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Digital Marketing Specialist with 4+ years of experience in online marketing, branding, and business strategy across music, media, and entertainment industries. Skilled in evaluating financial needs and implementing multi-pronged digital strategies that increase revenue and drive brand growth.

- (212) 256-1414
- lauren.chen@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/laurenchen/

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

September 2019–Present | Triangle Music Group, New York, NY **Digital Marketing Specialist**

- Manage digital sales and streaming accounts to improve brand positioning and growth
- Source and develop new strategic partnerships, social engagements, and advertising opportunities that generate new revenue streams
- Collaborate with internal departments to execute national advertising campaigns, plan global digital distribution, and redeploy a 1M+ consumer sales and marketing database

June 2017–August 2019 | Momo Software, New York, NY Digital Marketing Associate

- Worked with management to develop and apply digital marketing plans with a focus on driving acquisition and conversion
- Devised and implemented robust digital acquisition plans, ensuring precision in financial reporting, budgets, and forecasts
- Increased conversions by 15% from paid sources (PPC, Grant, Display, and VOD)
- Enhanced conversion rates by 12% via A/B testing landing pages for a better performing conversion funnel

June 2016–May 2017 | Kingston Digital, New York, NY

Marketing Intern

- Helped research, write, and edit blog posts for Kingston's website
- Determined relevant keywords and entities for pages using Semrush, Ahrefs, and Page Optimizer Pro
- Gathered and analyzed data from social media PPE campaigns

EDUCATION

May 2017

New York University,

New York, NY

Bachelor of Arts, Communications, Honors: cum laude (GPA: 3.6/4.0)

RELEVANT SKILLS

Digital Data Analytics

Digital Marketing

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe InDesign

AutoCAD

Rhinoceros

Microsoft Office

Slack



Dear Job Seeker,

The Corporate resume template is designed to make you appear professional and well-organized.

An easy-to-read sans-serif font and clear header hierarchy help hiring managers quickly determine if you're qualified for the job.

We suggest using the Corporate resume if you're aiming to join a company's leadership team as an executive or assistant manager.

If you're still struggling to write your resume, here are some free resources to help you put together a resume that shows employers you're the right person for the job:

- Free Resume Builder
- · How to Write a Resume
- Resume Samples by Industry

Once you have a great resume, pair it with a convincing cover letter using our matching 2021 cover letter template. Here are a few resources to help you write a cover letter that gives your application the boost it needs to land you an interview:

- · Cover Letter Builder
- How to Write a Cover Letter
- Cover Letter Examples by Industry

The Resume Genius team

Best regards,